http://www.kratosdefense.com/privacy-policy

AboutAboutAbout KratosDivisionsLocations & ContactsUpcoming EventsAbout KratosLeadershipContract VehiclesSmall BusinessEthics & ComplianceCorporate GovernanceContract VehiclesSeaPort-NxGGSATETRASATS-2Training System Contract IV (TSC IV)USV FoS IDIQ-MACDivisionsUnmanned SystemsSpace, Training, and CybersecurityDefense & Rocket Support ServicesMicrowave ElectronicsTurbine TechnologiesC5ISR SystemsUnmanned SystemsSystem IntegrationTrainingTest & ManufacturingSpace, Training, and CybersecuritySpaceTrainingCyberTrainingSimulation SystemsTraining ServicesSimulation Training PlatformTraining ServicesCurriculum DevelopmentAircrew Training CentersSustainment ServicesCyberFedRAMP Assessment & Advisory ServicesCloud SecurityFISMANIST/RMFCloud Security StrategySecurity Program ManagementPolicy & Procedure DevelopmentEnterprise Security ArchitectureFISMA ReadinessIncident ResponsePenetration TestingCDM/ISCMVulnerability AssessmentsApplication TestingDefense & Rocket Support ServicesAdvanced Concept Demonstration and TestAerosciences Test and Evaluation (T&E) Support and AnalysisEngineering, Design, & AnalysisEnterprise Services & Data Center SupportAcquisition & Program ManagementRapid Launch Vehicles and TargetsTurbine TechnologiesEngineering ServicesAbout KratosLeadershipContract VehiclesSeaPort-NxGGSATETRASATS-2Training System Contract IV (TSC IV)USV FoS IDIQ-MACSmall BusinessEthics & ComplianceCorporate GovernanceDivisionsUnmanned SystemsSystem IntegrationTrainingTest & ManufacturingSpace, Training, and CybersecuritySpaceTrainingSimulation SystemsTraining ServicesCurriculum DevelopmentAircrew Training CentersSustainment ServicesSimulation Training PlatformCyberFedRAMP Assessment & Advisory ServicesCloud SecurityFISMANIST/RMFCloud Security StrategySecurity Program ManagementPolicy & Procedure DevelopmentEnterprise Security ArchitectureFISMA ReadinessIncident ResponsePenetration TestingCDM/ISCMVulnerability AssessmentsApplication TestingDefense & Rocket Support ServicesAdvanced Concept Demonstration and TestAerosciences Test and Evaluation (T&E) Support and AnalysisEngineering, Design, & AnalysisEnterprise Services & Data Center SupportAcquisition & Program ManagementRapid Launch Vehicles and TargetsMicrowave ElectronicsTurbine TechnologiesEngineering ServicesC5ISR SystemsLocations & ContactsUpcoming EventsTechnologiesSystems & PlatformsSystems & PlatformsUnmanned SystemsSpace SystemsTraining SystemsC5ISR SystemsBallistic Missile Defense TargetsUnmanned SystemsAerialGroundAerialTactical UAVsSmall UAS SwarmingTethered Drone - AethonAerial TargetsGroundHigh Mobility Ground Vehicle TargetM-PAK Leader/Follower SystemAutonomous Truck Mounted Attenuator (ATMA)Space SystemsTurnkey Ground SystemsSpectrum MonitoringSatellite Command & ControlSpectrum RegulationOpenSpace Software-Defined PlatformOpenSpace Software-Defined PlatformOpenSpace PlatformVirtualized Ground StationEarth Observation Service ChainTraining SystemsSimulation SystemsSimulation Training PlatformTraining Product SupportSimulation SystemsAirGroundMaritimeSpaceAirMaintenance Training SystemsCollective Training SystemsAircrew Training SystemsC5ISR SystemsMissile Defense & RadarCommand & ControlUnmanned SystemsCombat SystemsMissile Defense & RadarMissile & Radar TestingUnmanned SystemsAerialTactical UAVsSmall UAS SwarmingTethered Drone - AethonAerial TargetsGroundHigh Mobility Ground Vehicle TargetM-PAK Leader/Follower SystemAutonomous Truck Mounted Attenuator (ATMA)Space SystemsTurnkey Ground SystemsSpectrum MonitoringSatellite Command & ControlSpectrum RegulationOpenSpace Software-Defined PlatformOpenSpace PlatformVirtualized Ground StationEarth Observation Service ChainTraining SystemsSimulation SystemsAirMaintenance Training SystemsCollective Training SystemsAircrew Training SystemsGroundMaritimeSpaceSimulation Training PlatformTraining Product SupportC5ISR SystemsMissile Defense & RadarMissile & Radar TestingCommand & ControlUnmanned SystemsCombat SystemsBallistic Missile Defense TargetsProductsProductsUAVsSpaceMicrowave ElectronicsUAVsAirLand & SeaRadiosAirAutopilots & Mission ComputersUAV Command & ControlTest SetsFlight Termination & Range SafetyTurbinesAutopilots & Mission ComputersUnmanned Vehicle Mission ComputerIntegrated Flight ControllerUAV Command & ControlPortable Command & ControlTransportable Command & ControlFixed Site Command & ControlTest SetsModel 38-4 C-Band TesterModel 41 C-Band Test SetMulti-Platform Vehicle Test SetFlight Termination Test Set915MHz Data Link Test SetFlight Termination & Range SafetyTurnkey Flight Termination SystemsModular Components & Test SetsLand & SeaGround Vehicle AutomationUGV Command and ControlSea Surface Vehicle AutomationGround Vehicle AutomationMulti-Platform Appliqué Kit (M-PAK)UGV Command and ControlBench Top SystemPortable Command & ControlSea Surface Vehicle AutomationHigh-Speed Maneuvering Surface Target (HSMST)RadiosAvionicsCDL Compliance Tester - CWCTSoftware-Defined RadiosAvionicsMulti-Service Data Link TransponderModel 290 Data Link TransponderC-Band Radar TransponderIdentify Friend Or Foe (IFF)Gulf Range Drone Control SystemModel 280-1 TransponderTarget Control TransponderSpaceSystemsNetworksSatellitesSignalsAntennasSupportSystemsTurnkey Ground SystemsSpectrum MonitoringSatellite Command & ControlSpectrum RegulationOpenSpace Software-Defined PlatformOpenSpace Software-Defined PlatformOpenSpace PlatformVirtualized Ground StationEarth Observation Service ChainNetworksCybersecurityNetwork ManagementNetwork DevicesCybersecurityCross Domain Guard - CyberC4:GuardCross Domain Enabler - CyberC4:ProxyNetwork ManagementMonitor & Control - CompassManager of Managers - NeuralStarUnified Management - OpenSpace OpsCenterNetwork DevicesNetwork Protocol Utility - DataDefenderDigitalIF - SpectralNetSerial-to-IP for Guard - quantumEdgeIP Access Gateway - ioPLEXData Transport Utility - T500MXSatellitesCommand & ControlTT&C Devices & SoftwareCommand & ControlSatellite Control - EPOCH IPSFlight Dynamics - OASYSSmall Satellite Control - quantumCMDTT&C Devices & SoftwareVirtual Front End Processor - quantumFEPVirtual TT&C - quantumRadioTailored TT&C Modem - T400XRStandard TT&C Modem - XR1SignalsSignal ProcessingTest & SimulationRF ManagementProtected CommunicationSignal ProcessingVirtual TT&C - quantumRadioMission Receiver - quantumMRDigital Recording Application - quantumDRAWideband Software Receiver - quantumRXT500RX Recorder FamilyWDR Wideband Data RecorderUWR Wideband Recording SystemTest & SimulationRF Channel SimulatorRadar Emulation Simulator - T400RF ManagementCarrier Monitoring - MonicsDigitizer - Monics 200VSAT Monitoring - SatGuardSignal Geolocation - satIDSignal Cancellation - SigXRF Monitoring Services - SSAAntennasIntegrated SystemsEarth Station AntennasSystem ControllersSpecialty Antennas and PedestalsHF AntennasRadar AntennasEarth Station AntennasFixed GEO Earth StationsFixed LEO/MEO Antenna SystemsTransportable Antenna SystemsTactical Antenna SystemsSpecialty Antennas and PedestalsTroposcatter AntennasDirection-Finding Spinning and Bifilar Helical AntennasAntenna PedestalsHF AntennasFixed Directional HF AntennasOmnidirectional HF AntennasRotatable Directional HF AntennasRadar AntennasWeather AntennasAir Traffic Control AntennasMicrowave ElectronicsMicrowave AttenuatorsMicrowave Frequency TranslatorsMicrowave IQ Vector Modulators and Bi-Phase ModulatorsMicrowave LimitersMicrowave Phase ShiftersMicrowave Solid State Power Amplifiers (SSPA)Microwave SourcesMicrowave SwitchesIntegrated Microwave Assembly (IMA)Millimeter Wave ComponentsMicrowave AttenuatorsAttenuators Selection GuideSwitched Bit Attenuators Selection GuideMicrowave Frequency TranslatorsFrequency Translators Selection GuideMicrowave IQ Vector Modulators and Bi-Phase ModulatorsIQ Vector Modulators Selection GuideMicrowave LimitersLimiters Selection GuideMicrowave Phase ShiftersMicrowave Phase Shifters Selection GuideMicrowave Solid State Power Amplifiers (SSPA)Microwave SSPA Selection GuideMicrowave SourcesDTOsFLOsMicrowave SynthesizersVCOsMicrowave SwitchesSPST thru SP16T Microwave Switch Selection GuideHigh & Medium Power Microwave Switch Selection GuideIntegrated Microwave Assembly (IMA)Amplitude Control Module (ACM)Beam Forming - For Phased Array RadarsFrequency ConvertersSwitched Filter BanksReceiver Wide BandRF Front EndTransceivers For Data-Links and Smart MunitionTransmit/Receive ModulesMillimeter Wave ComponentsMillimeter Wave SwitchesMillimeter Wave AttenuatorsModel 7050 Millimeter Wave 3 dB Quadrature CouplerCustom Millimeter Wave AssembliesMillimeter Wave Phase ShiftersUAVsAirAutopilots & Mission ComputersUnmanned Vehicle Mission ComputerIntegrated Flight ControllerUAV Command & ControlPortable Command & ControlTransportable Command & ControlFixed Site Command & ControlTest SetsModel 38-4 C-Band TesterModel 41 C-Band Test SetMulti-Platform Vehicle Test SetFlight Termination Test Set915MHz Data Link Test SetFlight Termination & Range SafetyTurnkey Flight Termination SystemsModular Components & Test SetsTurbinesLand & SeaGround Vehicle AutomationMulti-Platform Appliqué Kit (M-PAK)UGV Command and ControlBench Top SystemPortable Command & ControlSea Surface Vehicle AutomationHigh-Speed Maneuvering Surface Target (HSMST)RadiosAvionicsMulti-Service Data Link TransponderModel 290 Data Link TransponderC-Band Radar TransponderIdentify Friend Or Foe (IFF)Gulf Range Drone Control SystemModel 280-1 TransponderTarget Control TransponderCDL Compliance Tester - CWCTSoftware-Defined RadiosSpaceSystemsTurnkey Ground SystemsSpectrum MonitoringSatellite Command & ControlSpectrum RegulationOpenSpace Software-Defined PlatformOpenSpace PlatformVirtualized Ground StationEarth Observation Service ChainNetworksCybersecurityCross Domain Guard - CyberC4:GuardCross Domain Enabler - CyberC4:ProxyNetwork ManagementMonitor & Control - CompassManager of Managers - NeuralStarUnified Management - OpenSpace OpsCenterNetwork DevicesNetwork Protocol Utility - DataDefenderDigitalIF - SpectralNetSerial-to-IP for Guard - quantumEdgeIP Access Gateway - ioPLEXData Transport Utility - T500MXSatellitesCommand & ControlSatellite Control - EPOCH IPSFlight Dynamics - OASYSSmall Satellite Control - quantumCMDTT&C Devices & SoftwareVirtual Front End Processor - quantumFEPVirtual TT&C - quantumRadioTailored TT&C Modem - T400XRStandard TT&C Modem - XR1SignalsSignal ProcessingVirtual TT&C - quantumRadioMission Receiver - quantumMRDigital Recording Application - quantumDRAWideband Software Receiver - quantumRXT500RX Recorder FamilyWDR Wideband Data RecorderUWR Wideband Recording SystemTest & SimulationRF Channel SimulatorRadar Emulation Simulator - T400RF ManagementCarrier Monitoring - MonicsDigitizer - Monics 200VSAT Monitoring - SatGuardSignal Geolocation - satIDSignal Cancellation - SigXRF Monitoring Services - SSAProtected CommunicationAntennasIntegrated SystemsEarth Station AntennasFixed GEO Earth StationsFixed LEO/MEO Antenna SystemsTransportable Antenna SystemsTactical Antenna SystemsSystem ControllersSpecialty Antennas and PedestalsTroposcatter AntennasDirection-Finding Spinning and Bifilar Helical AntennasAntenna PedestalsHF AntennasFixed Directional HF AntennasOmnidirectional HF AntennasRotatable Directional HF AntennasRadar AntennasWeather AntennasAir Traffic Control AntennasSupportMicrowave ElectronicsMicrowave AttenuatorsAttenuators Selection GuideSwitched Bit Attenuators Selection GuideMicrowave Frequency TranslatorsFrequency Translators Selection GuideMicrowave IQ Vector Modulators and Bi-Phase ModulatorsIQ Vector Modulators Selection GuideMicrowave LimitersLimiters Selection GuideMicrowave Phase ShiftersMicrowave Phase Shifters Selection GuideMicrowave Solid State Power Amplifiers (SSPA)Microwave SSPA Selection GuideMicrowave SourcesDTOsFLOsMicrowave SynthesizersVCOsMicrowave SwitchesSPST thru SP16T Microwave Switch Selection GuideHigh & Medium Power Microwave Switch Selection GuideIntegrated Microwave Assembly (IMA)Amplitude Control Module (ACM)Beam Forming - For Phased Array RadarsFrequency ConvertersSwitched Filter BanksReceiver Wide BandRF Front EndTransceivers For Data-Links and Smart MunitionTransmit/Receive ModulesMillimeter Wave ComponentsMillimeter Wave SwitchesMillimeter Wave AttenuatorsModel 7050 Millimeter Wave 3 dB Quadrature CouplerCustom Millimeter Wave AssembliesMillimeter Wave Phase ShiftersInvestorsInvestorsInvestor RelationsPress ReleasesEvents & PresentationsFinancial InformationStock InformationInvestor FAQsFinancial InformationSEC FilingsAnnual ReportsQuarterly ResultsInvestor RelationsPress ReleasesEvents & PresentationsFinancial InformationSEC FilingsAnnual ReportsQuarterly ResultsStock InformationInvestor FAQsCareers
Privacy Policy
Kratos Defense & Security Solutions, Inc. and its subsidiaries (“Kratos,” “we,” or “us”) are committed to your privacy and protecting your personal data. This notice explains what personal data is collected and processed by Kratos. If you have any questions or concerns about the information in this notice, we encourage you to contact us.
Who is Kratos?
Kratos is a data controller of personal data we have collected. There are several different ways that you can contact us. You may contact us by mail or telephone at:
10680 Treena Street, 6th Floor
San Diego, CA 92131
Phone: 858.812.7300
Toll-Free: 866.606.KTOS
You may also contact us directly by completing a form, or preferably, email us at privacy@kratosdefense.com.
When Does This Privacy Notice Apply?
This notice applies to the processing by Kratos of all personal data of customers, suppliers, vendors, visitors, and other individuals. It does not apply to former, current, or prospective employees. Our privacy notice for job applicants can be found here. If you are a California resident, our CCPA notice can be found here.
What Personal Data Do We Process And For What Purpose?
When you directly interact with Kratos
For responding to inquiries or other communications we will process your name, contact details, and any other personal data you include in your communications.
For health, safety, and security, we process your name, contact details, company details, and your image through CCTV feeds when you visit our premises. In addition, if you visit one of our premises and connect to our IT network, we will process personal data sent from your device, such as your IP address. Such information is needed to provide you with internet access, to monitor your use of our information and communication systems to ensure compliance with our policies, and to ensure network and information security.
When you visit our website
Like most organizations, we use third-party service providers for analytics, which use cookies and similar technologies to automatically collect information when you visit our website, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address, and the domain name from which you accessed the site. When you access our website using a mobile device, information about the type of mobile device you are using is collected. Information is also collected about how you use our website, such as the date and time you visit the site, the areas or pages of the site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the site, the number of times you return to the site, and other click-stream data.
We collect this information to prevent or combat malicious activities, to understand how visitors are using our website, to optimize our website, and for marketing purposes.
If you do not want Kratos or our third-party service providers to use cookies during your visit to our website, your browser may allow you to disable or block certain cookies. Please refer to the help section of your browser for more information.
When you complete and submit a form on our website, we process the personal data that you included in the form so we can respond to your submission and for marketing purposes.
Kratos’ website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect information relating to children. If you believe that we have collected the information about a child under the age of 16, please contact us so that we can delete the information.
When you do business with us
Kratos collects personal data that you or your business provides us in connection with a business relationship between your company and Kratos. We process your contact details such as your address, email address, telephone number, and other business contact information, professional details such as your job title, and other categories of personal data that may be contained in written communications or disclosed orally.
We collect such personal data to assess whether to enter into a contact with your company, to enter into a contract with your company, to perform a contract with your company, to enforce contracts, to communicate with your company, to market to your company, and for internal management purposes.
We may also collect personal data about your from publicly available sources, such as LinkedIn.
In addition to the purposes for collecting personal data described under the three headings above, we may also process your personal data for the following purposes that we consider to be everyday business purposes:
For legal and regulatory compliance, including all uses and disclosures of personal data required by law or as reasonably needed for compliance with Kratos policies and procedures;
For audits, including financial, security, and compliance audits, and analysis and reporting;
To respond to and defend against legal claims; and
For corporate governance, including mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures.
On What Legal Basis Do We Process Your Personal Data?
We will only collect, process, and share your personal data where we are satisfied that we have an appropriate legal basis to do so. To process your personal data, we may rely on different legal basis, including:
Your consent (only when legally required or permitted). If we rely on your consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data, you may withdraw your consent at any time;
To establish a contractual relationship with you and to perform our obligations under such contract;
To comply with legal obligations and to establish, exercise, and defend our self from legal claims;
To pursue a legitimate interest, including:
Marketing to you or your company;
Entering into or performing a contract or commencing contractual negotiations as well as communicating with your company;
Responding to your inquiries or other direct communications with us
Ensuring our networks, information, and premises are secure.
If You Fail to Provide Your Information
Failing to provide your personal data to us when you:
Directly interact with us may prevent us from being able to respond to your inquiry or other communication;
Visit our website may prevent the website from performing optimally and may prevent us from contacting you about products you may be interested in.
Visit one of our facilities, we may prevent you from entering the facility beyond the reception area.
Or your company has a business relationship with us may prevent us from entering into a contract, performing under the applicable contract, or furthering our business relationship.
Disclosing Your Personal Information
Kratos does not sell, trade, or rent your information to third parties. Nor does Kratos maintain any relationships with any ad server companies, and no advertising appears on our website except our own.
We may share your personal data with third parties if required to perform a contract or take steps to enter into such contracts. For example, we may share the contact information of an employee of a business partner with our customer.
As described above, Kratos will share your personal data with certain third-party service providers when you visit our website. For analytics, we use Google Analytics and Act-On.
We will also disclose your information to the extent required by law and to comply with legitimate governmental requests, subpoenas, court orders, and to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
We will also disclose your information to third parties if we choose to sell, transfer, merge, or otherwise dispossess all or parts of our business or our assets.
Transferring Your Information
We transfer, process, and store information about you on servers located in the United States. We may also disclose or transfer your personal data to other entities within Kratos to fulfill one or more of the purposes described above. Kratos has self-certified under the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework for transferring information from the European Economic Area (EEA) to the United States and takes reasonable steps to ensure your information is not lost or misused during the transfer. To view the Kratos Privacy Shield certification, see www.privacyshield.gov.
Under certain circumstances, Kratos may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
If a third party service provider providing services on Kratos’ behalf processes personal data from the EEA in a manner that is inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, Kratos will be liable unless we can prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.
Rights You Have About Your Information
When your information is collected in the EEA, you have the right to: (1) request access to, correction, and/or erasure of your personal data; (2) object to our processing of your personal data; (3) request a copy of your personal data, or have a copy thereof sent to another controller, in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format under the right of data portability. You may exercise these rights by reaching out to us through one of the contact methods provided above.
In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Kratos commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EEA individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield notice should first contact Kratos at: privacy@kratosdefense.com.
Kratos has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.
The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has jurisdiction over Kratos’ compliance with the Privacy Shield.
Binding Arbitration
If you are located in the EEA and have exhausted all other means to resolve your concern regarding a potential violation of Kratos’ obligations under the Privacy Shield Principles, under certain circumstances you may seek resolution via binding arbitration. For additional information about the arbitration process, please visit the Privacy Shield website: https://www.privacyshield.gov.
Legitimate Interest and Direct Marketing Objections
For information collected in the EEA, you may object to Kratos processing your information where we are relying on a legitimate interest. We will stop processing your information unless we can demonstrate appropriate, overriding legitimate grounds for the processing or if needed for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.
You may also object to Kratos processing your information for purposes of direct marketing. Anyone can do this no matter where your information was collected by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link in any automated marketing email or by submitting your request to Kratos through one of the contact methods described above.
Security
Kratos takes reasonable and appropriate organizational and technical security measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in processing and the nature of such data, and comply with applicable laws and regulations.
How Long Do We Retain Your Personal Data?
We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the data was collected. When Kratos determines how long to retain your information, we will consider whether we have an active or potential business relationship with you, whether there are any legal obligations to which we are subject, and whether retention is prudent because of legal considerations (such as statute of limitations, litigation, or other investigations).
Covered Entities
The subsidiaries of Kratos Defense & Security Solutions that are also adhering to the Privacy Shield Principles are listed below:
Kratos Technology & Training Solutions, Inc.
Kratos Integral Systems International, Inc.
Kratos Integral Holdings, LLC
Kratos Networks, Inc.
Kratos Real Time Logic, Inc.
Kratos Communications, Inc.
Gichner Systems Group, Inc.
Gichner Systems International, Inc.
General Microwave Corporation
General Microwave Israel Corporation
Florida Turbine Technologies, Inc.
FTT America, LLC
KTT Core, Inc.
SAT Corporation
Kratos May Modify This Notice
We will modify this notice to the extent required to comply with laws or regulations applicable to Kratos, including any changes thereto. Kratos may also make insubstantial changes to this notice as it deems necessary. Any amended or modified notice will be posted to Kratos’ website.
Effective May 25, 2018
Last modified: January 1, 2020
Systems & Platforms
Unmanned Systems
Tactical UAVs
Small UAS Swarming
Aethon
Aerial Targets
